http://www.tefal.com/privacy

Forgotten password
You have lost your password. Thank you to give us your e-mail, we will send you your password by e-mail
Confirm
Cancel
Sleep user
You didn’t connect to the Tefal web site since one year. Please give us your mail to initialize your password
HOW TO USE
Find out tips & tricks to better use your product or take care of it
Personal Care
Nous sommes désolés ! La vente daccessoires nest pasDisponible en ligne pour la .Veuillez vous
Privacy Policy
1-What is a cookie ?
2. How do we use cookies?
3. How to change the settings of my computer with respect to the use of cookies and disable them?
4. Third party websites
5. Changes to our Privacy policy
6. Rights of access, correction deletion, and objection to the processing of your data
• TEFAL S.A.S (“we”, “our”), a Groupe SEB affiliate company, wishes to be as transparent as possible on how it collects and processes personal data of users browsing and/or using the services of the website www.tefal.comThe Privacy policy (“Policy”) set out below, describes how personal data collected in connection with this Website are used, disclosed to third parties by SEB DEVELOPPEMENT where appropriate, the measures taken to ensure their confidentiality and security, as well as your choices with respect to the collection and use of your personal data.In accordance with the French Data Protection Act (“Loi Informatique et Libertés”) n ° 78- 17 of 6 January 1978 as amended by the Act n° 2004-801 of 6 August 2004, this Website has been notified to the French Data Protection Authority (CNIL).1-What is a cookie ?
The www.tefal.com site uses cookies. Cookies are small files that are stored on users' computers notably in order to make their navigation on the website easier and personalize the service offered to them.The cookies of the website do not contain any data that allow to identify you personally, and are designed to be used by SEB DEVELOPPEMENT only. SEB DEVELOPPEMENT informs users that they may prevent the storage of cookies by changing their browser settings. However, in order to benefit from all the functionalities of the Website, you should set your browser to accept the cookies.2. How do we use cookies?
We use cookies to improve the information and services that we provide on the Website and also to make navigation on our Website easier, for instance to recognize you when you return to our Website and avoid logging-in if you have created a user account or to allow managing your shopping cart during your browsing session .This Website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service of Google Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses cookies, which are stored on your computer and which allow your use of the website to be analyzed. The information on your use of this website generated by this cookie (including your IP address) is transferred to and stored on a Google server in the USA. Google uses this information to evaluate your use of this website to compile reports on website activities for website owners and to provide other services for website and internet use.Google will make this information available to third parties if Google is required legally todo so or if Google contracts those parties to process data. Google will not link your IP address to any other data at Google Inc. You can prevent these cookies from being installed by configuring your browser accordingly. Please be advised that you may not be able to access all functions of this website if you do so. By using this website, you expressly allow Google to process data collected in the manner for the purposes mentioned above.In addition, we work with other companies that use tracking technologies (tracking) to serve, on our behalf, ads on the Internet. These companies may collect non-personally identifiable information about your visits on our Website and your interaction with our communications, such as advertising.3. How to change the settings of my computer with respect to the use of cookies and disable them?
You can set your computer in order to receive a warning each time a cookie is sent, or choose to disable all cookies. These operations can be performed by accessing your browser’s settings. Each browser being a little different, please consult the Help menu of your browser to learn how to manage your cookies as appropriate. If you disable cookies, you will not have access to many features that facilitate the use of this Website and some of our services will not function properly.4. Third party websites
Our Website may contain links to websites operated by third parties that are not subject to this Policy and where practices relating to the collection and use of personal data may differs from ours. Provided that we do not own nor operate such websites, we cannot be responsible for the use of your personal data by such third party websites. We recommend you to read information regarding the processing of personal data provided by these websites.5. Changes to our Privacy policy
If we decide to change our Privacy policy, we will post the new Policy on this Website. We recommend you to regularly check that our Privacy policy has not been modified. The last update was 2014-02-20.6. Rights of access, correction deletion, and objection to the processing of your data
In accordance with the French Data Protection Act (“Loi Informatique et Libertés”), , any person whose data are collected and processed on the Website has a right of access, correction, deletion of any personal data relating to him/her as well as a right to object upon legitimate grounds to the processing of his/her data. To exercise these rights, you can contact us by writing to the following address:GROUPE SEB, Direction des Marques, Marketing Digital.Les 4 M - Chemin du Petit BoisBP 17269134 ECULLY CEDEX FranceYou can also contact the consumer service.
delivery.information.popup.title
delivery.information.popup.text1
shipping.logistician.extlog
shipping.logistician.saplog
delivery.information.popup.text2
×
Login
Loading...
Find the instructions for use of your Tefal products.
Frequent questions
Get answers to your questions.
Contact
Our advisors are at your service.
